Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 1 and District 1 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 1 Locals, 2.
  - Local 110
    - Local 110 Outgoing Correspondence, 1939-1957 (Box 6, Folder 50)
      - Wodarski to David Lasky Regarding Factionalism, February 5, 1951; 24.
      - Wodarski to Francis Philipps Regarding Factionalism, February 5, 1951; 25.
      - Wodarski to Harold Weidemeyer Regarding Factionalism, February 5, 1951; 26.
    - Local 110 Receipts, 1938-1940 (Box 6, Folder 51)
      - Watson Gamelle, Receipt #4965, September 20, 1938; 1.
      - Gamelle, November 3, 1938-January 6, 1939; 2-4.
      - Gamelle with February 9, 1939, Receipt #5045, February 10, 1939; 5.
      - Gamelle, February 10-November 16, 1939; 6-15.
      - Gordon Garnett, November 22, 1939-April 23, 1940; 16-22.
      - Garnett with Letter to Julius Emspak Regarding Payment for UE News and March 1939 Per Capita Report, May 9, 1940; 23.
      - Garnett, May 20-August 20, 1940; 24-27.
    - Local 110 Per Capita Reports, April 1939-July 1940 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Local 110 Supply Requisitions, March 1939-April 1946 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Local 110 Notices of Delinquency, February 1939-May 1940 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Local 110 Report of Financial Secretary, September 1938-March 1939 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Local 110 David Scribner Memo to Janet with Receipt, February 1, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Local 111
    - Local 111 Officer Lists, 1942-1949 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - William Kirkpatrick to Julius Emspak Regarding Officer Lists, December 2, 1942; 1.
      - Gilbert Reagan to Edward Matthews Regarding Officer Lists, December 7, 1946; 2.
      - Executive Board to Matthews Regarding Officer Lists, December 29, 1947; 3.
      - Officers, May 20, 1948; 4.
      - Officers, July 21, 1948; 5.
      - Officers, December 20, 1948; 6.
      - Bertrand Hoffman to Emspak Regarding Officer Lists, December 20, 1948; 7.
      - Officers, February 23, 1949; 8.
      - Hoffman to Emspak Regarding Officer Lists, May 21, 1949; 9.
    - Local 111 Incoming Correspondence, 1939-1949 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - William Cahn to Gilbert Reagan Regarding Advertisements, February 20, 1946; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to George Hagensick Regarding Finances with Statement on Dues, Initiations and Employment Stamps, August 17, 1939; 2.
      - Emspak to Hagensick Regarding Finances, January 5, 1940; 3.
      - Emspak to Hagensick Regarding Finances, March 26, 1940; 4.
      - Emspak to Hagensick Regarding Supplies, June 14, 1940; 5.
      - Emspak to Hagensick Regarding Supplies, July 26, 1940; 6.
      - Emspak to William Kirkpatrick Regarding Finances, March 31, 1941; 7.
      - Emspak to Kirkpatrick Regarding Russian War Relief, October 7, 1942; 8.
      - Emspak to Alfred Meier Regarding Finances for Veterans, July 23, 1945; 9.
      - Emspak to Reagan Regarding Funds for Local 111 Westinghouse Strike, May 4, 1946; 10.
      - Emspak to Carlton Hooks Regarding Finances with Insured Parcel Notice, January 17, 1947; 11.
      - Emspak to Hooks Regarding Local 111 Officers, April 23, 1947; 12.
      - Emspak to Ralph Gumbert Regarding Local 111 Officers, January 29, 1948; 13.
      - James Matles to Reagan Regarding Supplies, March 18, 1946; 14.
      - Matles to Gumbert Regarding Organization Committee for GE Strike, December 1, 1947; 15.
      - Edward Matthews to Bertrand Hoffman Regarding Factionalism and Westinghouse Contracts, May 27, 1949; 16.
      - Matthews to Hoffman Regarding Factionalism and the Westinghouse Conference Board, June 7, 1949; 17.
      - A.L. Sokal to Local 111 Officers Regarding Article 19 Violation, May 19, 1949; 18.
      - Incoming Correspondence Envelopes, 1949; 19.
    - Local 111 Outgoing Correspondence, 1938-1949 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Charles Daly to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, October 24, 1938; 1.
      - Ralph Gumbert to Edward Matthews Regarding Local 111 Officers, April 2, 1947; 2.
      - Gumbert to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 15, 1948; 3.
      - George Hagensick to Emspak Regarding Supplies, May 26, 1939; 4.
      - Hagensick to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 23, 1939; 5.
      - Hagensick to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 10, 1939; 6.
      - Hagensick to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 23, 1940; 7.
      - Hagensick to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 29, 1940; 8.
      - Hagensick to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 24, 1940; 9.
      - Bertrand Hoffman to Emspak Regarding Local 111 Officers, April 9, 1949; 10.
      - Hoffman to Emspak Regarding Local 111 Officers, May 2, 1949; 11.
      - Hoffman to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism with the Westinghouse Conference Board, May 21, 1949; 12.
      - William Kirkpatrick to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 26, 1941; 13.
      - Kirkpatrick to Emspak Regarding Russian War Relief, September 30, 1942; 14.
      - Kirkpatrick to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 14, 1943; 15.
      - Kirkpatrick to Emspak Regarding Local 111 Officers, May 11, 1943; 16.
      - Alfred Meier and Leo Peirce to Emspak Regarding Local 111 Constitution, January 3, 1940; 17.
      - Peirce to Emspak Regarding People's Press, September 14, 1938; 18.
      - Peirce to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 11, 1938; 19.
      - Peirce to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 16, 1939; 20.
      - Peirce to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 13, 1939; 21.
      - Peirce to Emspak Regarding Supplies, March 28, 1939; 22.
      - Peirce to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 29, 1939; 23.
      - Peirce to Emspak Regarding Supplies, November 3, 1939; 24.
      - Peirce to Emspak Regarding Finances and UE News, December 14, 1939; 25.
      - Peirce to Emspak Regarding Supplies, January 8, 1940; 26.
      - Peirce to Emspak Regarding Supplies, June 17, 1940; 27.
      - Peirce to Emspak Regarding 1946 UE Convention, August 15, 1946; 28.
    - Local 111 Outgoing Correspondence, 1945-1949 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Gilbert Reagan to Edward Matthews Regarding Advertisements and Strikes at GE and Westinghouse, February 7, 1946; 1.
      - Reagan to Matthews Regarding Supplies, March 6, 1946; 2.
      - Executive Board to James Matles Regarding Organization of Philadelphia GE, November 24, 1947; 3.
      - Executive Board to Matthews Regarding Factionalism and the Westinghouse Conference Board, June 3, 1949; 4.
      - Financial Secretary to UE Regarding Supplies, July 5, 1945; 5.
    - Local 111 Correspondence, 1966-1971 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Local 111 Salary and Expense Letters, George Hagensick, May-October 1941 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Local 111 Receipts, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Leo Perice, September 16, 1938; 1.
      - George Hagensick, September 16, 1938; 2.
      - Peirce with Receipt #5171, October 10, 1938; 3.
      - Hagensick, October 17, 1938-January 13, 1939; 4-8.
      - Peirce, January 17-February 14, 1939; 9-10.
      - Hagensick with March 3, 1939, Receipt #6134, February 15, 1939; 11.
      - Hagensick, March 15, 1939; 12.
      - Peirce, March 30, 1939; 13.
      - Hagensick with Receipt #6396, April 14, 1939; 14.
      - Hagensick, April 15, 1939; 15.
      - Peirce, April 26, 1939; 16.
      - Hagensick, May 16-July 18, 1939; 17-19.
      - Peirce, April 26, 1939; 20.
      - Hagensick, August 16-November 1, 1939; 21-23.
      - Peirce, November 6, 1939; 24.
      - Hagensick with Receipt #8258, November 22, 1939; 25.
      - Hagensick, November 22-December 4, 1939; 26-27.
      - Peirce, December 18, 1939; 28.
    - Local 111 Receipts, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - George Hagensick, January 11-12, 1940; 1-2.
      - Hagensick with January 19, 1940, Receipt #8768, 3.
      - Hagensick, February 14-April 17, 1940; 4-6.
      - Hagensick with April 22, 1940, Receipt #9701, 7.
      - Hagensick, May 16, 1940; 8.
      - Hagensick with Receipt #9983, May 20, 1940; 9.
      - Hagensick, June 14, 1940; 10.
      - Hagensick with July 1, 1940, Receipt #10342, 11.
      - Hagensick, July 10, 1040; 12.
      - Hagensick with July 19, 1940, Receipt #10568, 13.
      - Hagensick, August 19, 1940; 14.
      - Leo Peirce, September 19, 1940; 15.
    - Local 111 Per Capita Reports, 1938-1940 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Per Capita Report, September 1938-june 1939; 1-10.
      - Per Capita Report with Form, July 11, 1939; 11.
      - Per Capita Report with August 14, 1939, Form, August 13, 1939; 12.
      - Per Capita Report with Form, September 12, 1939; 13.
      - Per Capita Report, September-November 1939; 14-16.
      - Per Capita Report with Form, November 1939-July 1940; 17-24.
      - Per Capita Report with Form, February 11, 1940; 19.
      - Per Capita Report, August 14, 1940; 25.
    - Local 111 Supply Requisitions, 1938-1940 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - George Hagensick, November 11, 1938; 1.
      - Leo Peirce, March 28-July 10, 1939; 2-4.
      - Harry Block, October 30, 1939; 5.
      - Peirce, January 24-September 12, 1940; 6-10.
    - Local 111 Stamps, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Harry Block, November 1, 1939; 1.
      - George Hagensick, November 22, 1939; 2.
    - Local 111 Shipment Notices, Harry Block, November 1, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Local 111 Notices of Delinquency, September 1939 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Local 111 Report of Financial Secretary, September 14, 1938-June 13, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Local 111 Credit Bills, September 9, 1938-August 25, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Local 111 Warning Notices, October 22, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Jos A. Adomaitis, October 22, 1969; 1.
      - Edw. Amoroso, October 22, 1969; 2.
      - Wayne M. Baggett, October 22, 1969; 3.
      - Ronald L. Bessetti, October 22, 1969; 4.
      - Eugene F. Boris, October 22, 1969; 5.
      - Lynol Bourgeois, October 22, 1969; 6.
      - Charles M. Brothman, October 22, 1969; 7.
      - Gerard J. Bulger, 8.
      - Matthew C. Calabria, October 22, 1969; 9.
      - Anthony Carrado, October 22, 1969; 10.
      - Joseph Catania, October 22, 1969; 11.
      - Victor C. Cerst, Jr., October 22, 1969; 12.
      - Kenneth W. Chew, October 22, 1969; 13.
      - Joseph R. Clifford, October 22, 1969; 14.
      - Arthur W. Conkright, October 22, 1969; 15.
      - Joseph J. Costa, October 22, 1969; 16.
      - Donald Covello, October 22, 1969; 17.
      - David L. Crawford, October 22, 1969; 18.
      - Louis E. Cropper, October 22, 1969; 19.
      - Anthony F. Czekanski, October 22, 1969; 20.
      - Gerald Davis, October 22, 1969; 21.
      - Ronald S. Dixon, October 22, 1969; 22.
      - Harold C. Dunn, October 22, 1969; 23.
      - Joseph F. Esposito, October 22, 1969; 24.
      - Rocco Ferrante, October 22, 1969; 25.
      - Frank Fillman, October 22, 1969; 26.
      - William M. Fischer, October 22, 1969; 27.
      - Russell J. Freiling, October 22, 1969; 28.
      - Arthur P. Gallagher, October 22, 1969; 29.
      - Robert D. Gatti, October 22, 1969; 30.
      - Raymond D. Geary, October 22, 1969; 31.
      - Edward J. Giannascoli, October 22, 1969; 32.
      - Edward Grabarski, October 22, 1969; 33.
      - Ronald Gramiak, October 22, 1969; 34.
      - Carl Green, October 22, 1969; 35.
      - Charles R. Greenan, October 22, 1969; 36.
      - Theodore Gross, October 22, 1969; 37.
      - John J. Grzib, October 22, 1969; 38.
      - James L. Gushue, October 22, 1969; 39.
      - Phillip L. Haines, October 22, 1969; 40.
      - Ralph W. Hargreaves, October 22, 1969; 41.
      - Albert Helmes, October 22, 1969; 42.
      - Francis Hess, October 22, 1969; 43.
      - Ronald Holt, October 22, 1969; 44.
      - Richard E. Holmes, October 22, 1969; 45.
      - Arthur C. Hopson, October 22, 1969; 46.
      - Francis J. Huber, October 22, 1969; 47.
      - Joseph W. Hughes, October 22, 1969; 48.
      - Donald A. Hummel, October 22, 1969; 49.
      - Ramiro Jimenez, October 22, 1969; 50.
      - Richard H. Junkerman, October 22, 1969; 51.
    - Local 111 Warning Notices, October 22, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - John M. Kirsch, October 22, 1969; 1.
      - Richard C. Krumin, October 22, 1969; 2.
      - Geo. L. Lemons, October 22, 1969; 3.
      - Wm. J. Madden, October 22, 1969; 4.
      - Stephen F. Marty, October 22, 1969; 5.
      - George A. Mauger, October 22, 1969; 6.
      - James A. McClintock, October 22, 1969; 7.
      - Martin D. McClinton, October 22, 1969; 8.
      - Joseph F. McCowan, October 22, 1969; 9.
      - Jas. E. McCown, October 22, 1969; 10.
      - Alfred F. Miller, October 22, 1969; 11.
      - Dominic J. Miriello, October 22, 1969; 12.
      - Alan W. Montgomery, October 22, 1969; 13.
      - Frank M. Morgan, October 22, 1969; 14.
      - Lawrence J. Moses, October 22, 1969; 15.
      - Dan J. Neel, October 22, 1969; 16.
      - Lenord E. Nicholson, October 22, 1969; 17.
      - Jas. A. Paisley, October 22, 1969; 18.
      - Dorance J. Patterson, October 22, 1969; 19.
      - Albert B. Peters, October 22, 1969; 20.
      - Anthony G. Pologruto, October 22, 1969; 21.
      - Gene E. Raffensperger, October 22, 1969; 22.
      - Fremont R. Robeson, October 22, 1969; 23.
      - Alonzo F. Robinson, October 22, 1969; 24.
      - John Romolini, October 22, 1969; 25.
      - Frank Rubbs, October 22, 1969; 26.
      - Russell Rubbs, October 22, 1969; 27.
      - Terrence P. Sack, October 22, 1969; 28.
      - Christian Shinn, October 22, 1969; 29.
      - William J. Shoemaker, October 22, 1969; 30.
      - James Sickels, October 22, 1969; 31.
      - Harry C. Simpkins, Jr., October 22, 1969; 32.
      - Michael T. Sitter, October 22, 1969; 33.
      - Harry Starnes, October 22, 1969; 34.
      - Ronald C. Stiles, October 22, 1969; 35.
      - Lloyd N. Strock, October 22, 1969; 36.
      - Nicholas T. Test, October 22, 1969; 37.
      - Albert L. Thomas, October 22, 1969; 38.
      - Robert L. Thompson, October 22, 1969; 39.
      - James Valloreo, October 22, 1969; 40.
      - Donald W. Vance, October 22, 1969; 41.
      - Frank P. Varsaci, October 22, 1969; 42.
      - Edw. L. Walker, October 22, 1969; 43.
      - Roy E. Weidenmoyer, October 22, 1969; 44.
      - Harry E. Wicks, October 22, 1969; 45.
      - Joseph T. Winner, October 22, 1969; 46.
      - Thomas E. Wise, October 22, 1969; 47.
    - Local 111 Warning Notices, October 29, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - John J. Adamaitis, October 29, 1969; 1.
      - Robt. E. Ade, October 29, 1969; 2.
      - Fredk. M. Barker, October 29, 1969; 3.
      - Jos. M. Broderick, October 29, 1969; 4.
      - Richard F. Bruns, October 29, 1969; 5.
      - John N. Bucceri, Jr., October 29, 1969; 6.
      - Adrian Buyser, Jr., October 29, 1969; 7.
      - Robt. J. Cants, October 29, 1969; 8.
      - Gerald S. Chandler, October 29, 1969; 9.
      - Robt. Cheeseman, October 29, 1969; 10.
      - Joseph F. Cirillo, October 29, 1969; 11.
      - Nelson A. Collins, October 29, 1969; 12.
      - Louis J. Conte, October 29, 1969; 13.
      - Norman Craig, October 29, 1969; 14.
      - Peter R. Daraio, October 29, 1969; 15.
      - Michael T. DeLuccia, October 29, 1969; 16.
      - Paul L. Densten, October 29, 1969; 17.
      - Santino (Sam) DiGiacomo, October 29, 1969; 18.
      - Stephen L. Dixon, October 29, 1969; 19.
      - Alexander M. Farley, October 29, 1969; 20.
      - Robert Feller, October 29, 1969; 21.
      - David C. Fischer, October 29, 1969; 22.
      - George Fortune, October 29, 1969; 23.
      - Thos. E. Garrett, October 29, 1969; 24.
      - Jos. A. Gaylord, Jr., October 29, 1969; 25.
      - Carlton B. Giberson, October 29, 1969; 26.
      - Jas. A. Grasso, October 29, 1969; 27.
      - John J. Grasso, October 29, 1969; 28.
      - Mitchell J. Gray, October 29, 1969; 29.
      - Donald E. Haines, October 29, 1969; 30.
      - Paul J. Hartig, October 29, 1969; 31.
      - Robt. P. Hartzell, October 29, 1969; 32.
      - James E. Helveston, October 29, 1969; 33.
      - Geo. E. Hoban, October 29, 1969; 34.
      - R. Stephen Holmes, October 29, 1969; 35.
      - Wm. G. Ifill, October 29, 1969; 36.
      - Jos. A. Kendall, October 29, 1969; 37.
      - Robt. O. Kline, October 29, 1969; 38.
    - Local 111 Warning Notices, October 29, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Thos. Lanute, October 29, 1969; 1.
      - Walter B. Little, Jr., October 29, 1969; 2.
      - Ivan R. Lloyd, October 29, 1969; 3.
      - Saml. L. Long, October 29, 1969; 4.
      - Wm. R. Lynn, October 29, 1969; 5.
      - Raymond J. Mancinelli, October 29, 1969; 6.
      - Gene J. Martinelli, October 29, 1969; 7.
      - Henry Matousch, October 29, 1969; 8.
      - Bob F. Moore, October 29, 1969; 9.
      - James E. Moore, October 29, 1969; 10.
      - Wm. Moore, October 29, 1969; 11.
      - Albert J. Morrone, October 29, 1969; 12.
      - Edw. J. Nasser, October 29, 1969; 13.
      - Jos. R. Natale, October 29, 1969; 14.
      - Fred E. Neumann, October 29, 1969; 15.
      - Carl H. Nicholson, October 29, 1969; 16.
      - Herbert J. Nolan, October 29, 1969; 17.
      - Michael J. Nolan, October 29, 1969; 18.
      - Thos. A. Oatman, October 29, 1969; 19.
      - John G. O'Brien, October 29, 1969; 20.
      - Anthony J. Passalaqua, October 29, 1969; 21.
      - Paul J. Passalaqua, October 29, 1969; 22.
      - Raymond E. Pieri, October 29, 1969; 23.
      - Harry Richartz, October 29, 1969; 24.
      - Rice Rives, October 29, 1969; 25.
      - Juan R. Rodriguez, October 29, 1969; 26.
      - Franklin I. Shanks, October 29, 1969; 27.
      - Chas. W. Shubert, October 29, 1969; 28.
      - Jas. F. Sickels, Jr., October 29, 1969; 29.
      - Irving L. Smith, October 29, 1969; 30.
      - Robt. E. Spicer, October 29, 1969; 31.
      - Harold Taylor, October 29, 1969; 32.
      - Wendell W. Theriault, October 29, 1969; 33.
      - Harry C. Trunell, III, October 29, 1969; 34.
      - Frank L. Willis, October 29, 1969; 35.
      - H. Walter Wooden, Jr., October 29, 1969; 36.
      - Macy P. Wright, Jr., October 29, 1969; 37.
      - Peter G. Zizak, October 29, 1969; 38.
    - Local 111 Warning Notices, October 27, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Ernest T. Bodine, October 27, 1969; 1.
      - John Hartner, October 27, 1969; 2.
      - John H. Summers, October 27, 1969; 3.
      - Howard Williams, October 27, 1969; 4.
    - Local 111 Warning Notices, December 1, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Carmen L. Dottoli, December 1, 1969; 1.
      - Wm. W. Owens, December 1, 1969; 2.
      - Bruno F. Rakowski, December 1, 1969; 3.
    - Local 111 Court Affidavits, Johns-Manville Products Corporation vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America Local 111, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Local 111 Johns-Manville Strike, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Local 112
    - Local 112 Officers Lists, November 12, 1944-1949 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Local 112 Incoming Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Harry Block to Ruth Ratan Regarding Factionalism and the War Labor Board, November 30, 1943; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to George Breiner Regarding Supplies, January 4, 1939; 2.
      - Emspak to Mamie Puziene Regarding Unemployment, January 17, 1939; 3.
      - Emspak to Breiner Regarding Unemployment, February 16, 1939; 4.
      - Emspak to Breiner Regarding Finances, April 20, 1939; 5.
      - Emspak to Local 112 Regarding Finances, June 26, 1939; 6.
      - Emspak to Breiner Regarding Labor Education, August 22, 1939; 7.
      - Emspak to Breiner Regarding Finances, April 18, 1940; 8.
      - Emspak to Hilda Shuck Regarding Supplies and Unemployment, April 30, 1940; 9.
      - Emspak to Shuck Regarding Supplies, May 23, 1940; 10.
      - Emspak to Shuck Regarding Finances and Mailing List, October 14, 1940; 11.
      - Emspak to Breiner Regarding Mailing List and Finances, November 1, 1940; 12.
      - Emspak to Breiner Regarding Finances, August 15, 1941; 13.
      - Emspak to Breiner Regarding Inter-union Relations, June 23, 1941; 14.
      - Emspak to Ernest Moyer Regarding War Labor Board, December 2, 1943; 15.
      - Emspak to Ratan Regarding War Labor Board Contracts at Local 112 Magnetic Winding, December 2, 1943; 16.
      - Emspak to Florence Ricker Regarding Finances and Staff Finances, April 3, 1944; 17.
      - Emspak to Peter Besch Regarding Finances, November 15, 1944; 18.
      - Emspak to Ricker Regarding Veterans and Finances, July 10, 1945; 19.
      - Emspak to Shuck Regarding Veterans and Finances, March 28, 1946; 20.
      - Harry Jones to Mac Levitt Regarding War Labor Board, October 21, 1942; 21.
      - Jack McDonough to Breiner Regarding Organization at Metropolitan Hinge, October 9, 1942; 22.
      - David Scridner to Mac Levitt Regarding National Labor Relations Board, October 29, 1942; 23.
      - A.N. Townsen to Ricker Regarding Wages, April 4, 1944; 24.
    - Local 112 Outgoing Correspondence, 1939-1945, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Peter Besch to Julius Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Finances, November 29, 1944; 1.
      - George Breiner to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 24, 1939; 2.
      - George Breiner to UE Regarding Supplies, August 1, 1939; 3.
      - George Breiner to UE Regarding Labor Education, August 18, 1939; 4.
      - George Breiner to Emspak Regardng Finances, August 18, 1939; 5.
      - George Breiner to James Matles Regarding "Your Union at Work", May 10, 1940; 6.
      - Frank Breiner to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, September 19, 1940; 7.
      - Frank Breiner to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Finances, October 22, 1940; 8.
      - Frank Breiner to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Mailing List, January 20, 1941; 9.
      - Frank Breiner to Matles Regarding Organization in Easton and Collective Bargaining at Local 112, April 23, 1941; 10.
      - Frank Breiner to Emspak Regarding UE News and Finances, July 23, 1941; 11.
      - Frank Breiner to Emspak Regarding Local 451 and Withdrawal Cards with June 9, 1943, Emspak Letter to John McDonough, May 19, 1943; 12.
      - Sam Goldberg to Emspak Regarding War Labor Board, February 24, 1944; 13.
      - Mac Levitt to Harry Jones Regarding War Labor Board, October 22, 1942; 14.
      - Levitt to Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Metropolitan Hinge, October 28, 1942; 15.
      - Jack McDonough to Harry Block Regarding Organization at Metropolitan Hinge, October 22, 1942; 16.
      - Carl Re to Jerold Mooney Regarding Reservations, 17.
      - Florence Ricker to Emspak Regarding Change of Address, February 3, 1944; 18.
      - Ricker to Emspak Regarding War Labor Board, Wages, and Contracts at Local 112 with February 10, 1944, Norma Gould Letter to Carl Bersing, February 8, 1944; 19.
      - Ricker to Emspak Regarding Change of Address, February 13, 1944; 20.
      - Ricker to Emspak Regarding Wages, Classifications, and Staff Finances, March 1944; 21.
      - Ricker to T. Neill Regarding Veterans and Finances, July 2, 1945; 22.
    - Local 112 Outgoing Correspondence, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - Ruth Ratan to Emspak Regarding War Labor Board, Factionalism, and Contracts at Local 112, November 29, 1943; 1.
      - Ratan to UE Regarding Membership Meeting, December 5, 1943; 2.
    - Local 112 Salary/Expense Letters, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - Hilda Schuck, February 18, 1941; 1.
      - Viola Feltman, August 19, 1941; 2.
    - Local 112 Receipts, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - Mamie Puziene, September 23-November 18, 1938; 1-3.
      - George Breiner, December 21, 1938; 4.
      - Puziene, January 13-March 21, 1939; 5-7.
      - Breiner, April 20, 1939; 8.
      - Puziene, April 20, 1939; 9.
      - Puziene, with June 21, 1939, Receipt #6960, June 22, 1939; 10.
      - Puziene, June 26-December 8, 1939; 11-17.
    - Local 112 Receipts (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - George Breiner, January 15, 1940; 1.
      - Mamie Puziene, January 24, 1940; 2.
      - Breiner with Application for Trade Union Facts, February 26, 1940; 3.